Peace and Justice Studies Records UA086
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2015; UA086.009; Bryan, Dale; 6 Linear Feet
  This series contains the files of Dale Bryan, Assistant Director of the Peace and Justice Studies (PJS) program until 2017. His files include PJS curriculum development, syllabi, and course information; PJS program and event files; information on PJS-related conferences and seminars held at Tufts; PJS and Center for Interdisciplinary Studies board minutes and grant files; and personal writings.
  - CIS Board minutes and grant files; PJS Executive Board minutes; course files; Projects for Peace student grant proposals, circa 1999 -- 2013; UA086.009.018; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 18)
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Events, conferences, seminars, circa 1989 -- 2015; UA086.009.019; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 19)
  - Conferences; River Institute/MRWA; PJS program, course, curriculum files; project and event files; Graduation Pledge Alliance, circa 1989 -- 2011; UA086.009.020; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 20)
  - Project and event files; Peace Games; syllabi, circa 2000 -- 2015; UA086.009.021; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 21)
  - Dale Bryan's writings; early PJS curriculum development, circa 1980 -- 2015; UA086.009.022; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 22)